

Ahmed A.
Software and Machine Learning Engineer

General info

Work experience Location

6 years total Cairo, Egypt

Time zone: UTC+2

Top technologies

Python	5+ years experience	1 2 3 4 5+
API Development	5+ years experience	12345+
SQL	5+ years experience	12345+
Machine Learning	5+ years experience	12345+
Data Science	5+ years experience	12345+

Technologies



Bio

Main areas of expertise

Software and Machine Learning Engineering.

Main tech stack

- Python: >5 years of professional experience
- Machine learning: >4 years of professional experience
- SQL: >4 years of professional experience

Jobs of interest

I'm interested in Senior developer jobs, where I work with my main technologies.

Experience

Co-Founder	05/2022 - now
B2Bya	6 months
Information Technology Specialist	12/2021 - now
Energya ElSewedy Helal	11 months
Machine Learning Engineer	02/2019 - 12/2021
Freelance	2 years and 10 months
Machine Learning Engineer	03/2018 - 01/2019
Louder Pages formerly F123 Consulting	10 months
Machine Learning Researcher	09/2017 - 12/2018
Egypt Scholars Inc.	1 year and 3 months
Chatbot Developer	08/2017 - 02/2018
WideBot	6 months
Android Developer	06/2016 - 07/2017
Freelance	1 year and 1 month

Education

Ain Shams University 01/2014 - 01/2016

Languages

English Working proficiency

Arabic Native